<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FiveNightsEscape</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
    <string name="health_3">Health: 3</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="_00_00s">00:00s</string>
    <string name="easy">Easy</string>
    <string name="hard">Hard</string>
    <string name="medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="level">Level: %1$d</string>
    <string name="how_to_play">
        <b>How to Play</b>\n\n
        Welcome to <b>Five Nights Escape</b>! Your goal is to survive as long as possible while avoiding monsters on the map. Here s how to play:\n\n
        <b>Basics</b>\n
        - The game revolves around surviving and escaping monsters that appear on the map.\n
        - You start with <b>3 hearts</b>.\n
        - Your goal is to <b>survive</b> as long as possible.\n\n
        <b>Difficulty</b>\n
        - Choose your difficulty level in the main menu. The difficulty determines how often more challenging monsters spawn.\n\n
        <b>Gameplay</b>\n
        - The game utilizes the <b>Google Maps API</b> to track your position and update monster movement accordingly.\n
        - Hearts: You start with <b>3 hearts</b>. Your task is to keep them throughout the game.\n
        - Timer: Track how long you ve survived.\n
        - Level Indicator: Display your current level on the main UI.\n\n
        <b>Monsters</b>\n
        - Monsters spawn based on random chances at fixed intervals. There are three types:\n
            - <b>Standing Monster:</b> Attacks if you enter its visual range.\n
            - <b>Chasing Monster:</b> Pursues you until you re out of its alert distance.\n
            - <b>Wandering Monster:</b> Moves randomly and attacks if a player is detected nearby.\n\n
        <b>Game Over</b>\n
        - Once you run out of hearts, you die, going back to the start menu and losing all progress towards your run.\n\n
        <b>Get Started</b>\n
        - Choose Difficulty: Select your preferred difficulty level.\n
        - Start the Game: Press the <b>Start</b> button to begin your escape, or swipe from left to right.\n\n
        <b>Tips</b>\n
        - Keep an eye on your hearts; losing them means <b>game over</b>.\n
        - Use the map to plan your escape routes.\n
        - Higher difficulty levels bring more challenging monsters.\n\n
        Survive as long as you can, and good luck escaping the <b>Five Nights monsters</b>!
    </string>
</resources>